(Sheldon:)but you can trust him
with your life.
(Sheldon:)And he does more things for you
than I can even begin to list.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, he's drinking it.
(gunfire sounding on videogame)
(Howard:)Look at this.
(Howard:)Trent is rebuilding
a vintage motorcycle.
(Dave:)Hmm.
That is so cool!
(Raj:)Old broken things
are so much better
(Raj:)than new things that work.
(Bernadette:)Who's Trent?
(Howard:)Oh, he's our fan.
(Bernadette:)Fan of what?
WOLOWITZ: Uh...
(laughs): Did you forget?
We're in a band.
(Bernadette:)You mean because you played one
time in the comic book store?
(Howard:)And at the children's hospital
until they asked us to leave.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Hey,
(Raj:)dude, Trent just checked in at
the coffee shop on Fair Oaks.
(Howard:)Really? You want to go
down there and meet him?
(Bernadette:)Are you stalking him?
That's creepy.
(Raj:)It's not creepy.
(Raj:)I built a Footprints on the Moon
fan page, Trent joined it.
(Howard:)After that, all I did was
check out his profile,
(Howard:)go back in the archive
of his feed